<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TeamProject</string>
    <string name="login">login</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forget Password</string>
    <string name="main_bottom_castles">Alnwick | Aukland | Bamburgh | Barnard</string>
    <string name="home_page_notice">Notice: The trip to Alnwick Castle in 12:00 is canceled!</string>

    <string name="alnwick_intro">
        Alnwick Castle is a castle and country house in Alnwick in the English county of Northumberland.
        It is the seat of The 12th Duke of Northumberland, built following the Norman conquest and
        renovated and remodelled a number of times. It is a Grade I listed building and as of 2012
        received over 800,000 visitors per year when combined with adjacent attraction The Alnwick Garden.
    </string>

    <string name="auckland_intro">
        Auckland Castle, which is also known as Auckland Palace and to people that live locally as the
        Bishop Castle or Bishop Palace, is located in the town of Bishop Auckland in County Durham,
        England. In 1832, this castle replaced Durham Castle as the official residence of the Bishops
        of Durham. It is now a tourist attraction, but still houses the Bishop offices; the Castle is
        a Grade I listed building.
    </string>

    <string name="bamburgh_intro">
        Bamburgh Castle is a castle on the northeast coast of England, by the village of Bamburgh in
        Northumberland. It is a Grade I listed building.\n

        The site was originally the location of a Celtic Brittonic fort known as Din Guarie and may
        have been the capital of the kingdom of Bernicia from its foundation in c. 420 to 547. After
        passing between the Britons and the Anglo-Saxons three times, the fort came under Anglo-Saxon
        control in 590. The fort was destroyed by Vikings in 993, and the Normans later built a new
        castle on the site, which forms the core of the present one. After a revolt in 1095 supported
        by the castle\'s owner, it became the property of the English monarch.\n

        In the 17th century, financial difficulties led to the castle deteriorating, but it was restored
        by various owners during the 18th and 19th centuries. It was finally bought by the Victorian era
        industrialist William Armstrong, who completed its restoration. The castle still belongs to the
        Armstrong family and is open to the public.

    </string>

    <string name="barnard_intro">
        Barnard Castle is a market town on the north bank of the River Tees, in County Durham,
        Northern England. The town is named after and built around a medieval castle ruin. The towns
        Bowes Museums has an 18th-century Silver Swan automaton exhibit and paintings by Goya and El Greco.\n

        It sits on the opposite bank to Startforth and is 21 miles south west of the county
        town of Durham. Nearby towns include Bishop Auckland to the north east, Darlington to the
        east and Richmond in North Yorkshire to the south-east. The largest employer is GlaxoSmithKline,
        with a manufacturing facility on the town outskirts.

    </string>

</resources>